Happy New Year.
Happy New Year, Father.
To another glorious year, Father.
You look quite radiant today.
To another glorious year.
Indeed. I am glad to see that
you're all doing well.
Oh, there's not enough sake.
Allow me.
Oh, no, Neko-san.
You're just getting over an illness.
No, I'm quite all right now.
Whee! Vroom!
Oh, my. Are you all right?
Hey! What do you think you're doing, Shouta?
You need to behave today!
Yuriko-neesan?
Oh! Is that you, Neko-chan?
What a surprise that was!
You've gotten so pretty!
I guess we haven't seen
each other since your wedding.
Yes. I think you were about
Shouta's age back then.
Yes, I was quite small and round.
Yes, exactly! It's so hard to picture that now!
Yes...
#7 "There's No Point in This Confession"
You don't know what's causing it?
Yes. It's not unreasonable to think that
you've suddenly developed
some sort of food allergy.
But considering where your hives
appeared, that likelihood is low.
I see.
At your age, your hormones
can become a wreck at any time.
It's not uncommon for even a
little bit of stress to cause hives.
A little bit of stress?
Anyway, take it easy for a while,
and we'll keep an eye on this
as we wait for your blood tests.
Uh, okay.
Please come see me again in a week.
If anything else happens in that time,
we'll do a more thorough checkup.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Stress, huh?
Aw, I should've gotten anmitsu.
The ozouni looked good, too.
Right?
The first shrine visit of the year...
Did you go already, President?
Nope.
For the first three days of the year,
we go to see relatives on
both sides of my family.
That's where I get to experience
the grueling activity of
babysitting all the little brats under
the guise of "New Year's greetings."
I've heard of people gaining
a little weight over New Year's,
but I guess you get a diet
and a workout for yours.
What about you, Kojuurou-kyun?
I basically spent all my
time in front of the TV.
I binge-watched The Solitary Gourmand.
Aw... We just rang in the new year,
so I want to have some fun and
celebrate with all of you guys.
Like when we all went to the ocean?
Hey, why don't we all do our
first shrine visit together?
Huh?
Yeah, let's do it!
Hey, isn't that...
Messages
Tae
Edit
Hey, look behind you!
At the café!
Tae
Behind me?
I thought it was up... but it was down.
And then...
My stomach hurts so much,
I can't move
There's a present for you downstairs
in my coat pocket
Messages
Makabe Masamune
Edit
There's a present for you downstairs
in my coat pocket
Please just take that and
leave for today
I'm really sorry
Also, Happy Birthday
A present?
Is this it?
I'm going to get revenge
on that woman!!
Aki-sama.
See you again next week!
Huh? What?
This program was brought to you
by the following sponsors.
The TV show is over.
Huh? Oh...
I guess there aren't many
interesting shows during New Year's.
It's nothing but comedy shows and sports.
Are you not going to go out anywhere?
Where in the world am I going
to go in this cold weather?
You don't have any plans?
No, not really.
January 4
It's not like I have any plans...
Happy New Year!
H-Happy New Year...
Er, you guys sure have a lot
of energy so early in the year.
Well, the president and I were just talking.
Talking? About what?
We wanted to do our first
shrine visit with everyone.
Masamune-kun, did you already
do your first shrine visit?
No, I just stayed at home for
the first three days of the year.
Then why don't we all go together?
Huh? Right now?
Okay, let's do it.
Yay!
Then let's go ahead and invite
Adagaki-san and the others, too.
Just like when we went to the ocean!
Huh?
Well?
E-Er, I mean, Adagaki-san seems busy,
so I'm sure Master... Koiwai-san is, too.
I see...
Then let's at least see if
Fujinomiya-san is available.
Come now, Neko-san.
How am I supposed to move if
you're holding onto me so tightly?
You're so spooked by everything.
Aw, how cute!
She's probably around the
same age as my Maa-kun.
Oh, Maa-kun! Come here a second.
Did you find the roast beef?!
Maa-kun, say hi. This is
Fujinomiya-san's daughter, Neko-chan.
Aw, but where's the beef?
Go on, Neko-chan.
Want some?
Come now, Masamune! You can't
just go putting food in your pockets!
What? Did you want some, too, Dad?
Oh, my. Maa-kun's pockets
are like a squirrel's cheeks!
HNY! Masamune-kun, Kojuurou-kyun,
and I are about to do our first shrine visit.
Did you want to come with us?
Tae
With Masamune-sama?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year!
I-I look forward to spending another
year with you, Fujinomiya-san.
Yes, likewise. To another year.
I look forward to spending another year
with you, as well, Masamune-sama.
Likewise.
Um... Are Adagaki-san and
Koiwai-san not joining us?
Oh, uh, something came up...
Okay! Onward to our first shrine visit!
I'm gonna draw a great blessing in my fortune!
Yeah!
Now it just sounds like our motive
is to draw a great blessing.
Fortunes
Luck
Great Blessing
Mid Blessing
Luck
Future Blessing
Chocolate Bananas
Specialty Yakisoba
Step right up!
How many you want? One? Two?
What did you wish for, Masamune-kun?
All right, one it is.
What else?
That'll be 500 yen.
It must've been to be able to
have fun with Adagaki-san, right?
Huh? Oh, yeah, something... like that.
Oh! Hey, look!
Hagoita! Hey! Let's play Hanetsuki!
Sure, sounds fun!
Oh, but Fujinomiya-san, do you think
you'll physically be able to play?
Yes, a little exercise will be just fine.
And this is quite nostalgic.
The Annual New Year
Fujinomiya Clan
Grand Hanetsuki
Tournament
The Annual New Year Fujinomiya Clan
Grand Hanetsuki Tournament!
Back when I was little,
everyone in my family, as well as
everyone who worked at our mansion,
would have a grand hanetsuki tournament.
Everyone in the Fujinomiya family?
I can't even imagine.
I think there's actually a park nearby.
Well, it looks like the president
and I are on a team.
The losing team has to buy everyone drinks.
Bring it on.
Okay, here we go.
Hi-yah!
Go!
Whoa... There!
Take that!
Kojuurou-kyun!
S-Sorry!
Okay, now I'm gonna get serious!
Kojuurou-kyun...
Man, I'm pretty exhausted.
Your face looks awful, Masamune-sama.
Look who's talking, Fujinomiya-san.
Man, I haven't laughed like this in a while.
You haven't?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here. We lost, so this is on us.
Were you okay with a
sports drink, Masamune-kun?
No, I'd prefer green tea,
since it helps with burning fat.
See you later!
Well, see you when the new term starts.
See ya.
Man, I think I had a bit too much fun.
The hives are... gone?
I guess I ended up not seeing
Adagaki-san since Christmas Eve.
Hey, I think they're over there.
Really?
Exam Room 1
Please come see me again in two weeks.
I will. Thank you very much.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Shidou.
My lady.
There were no issues. Let's go.
Please go in, my lady.
Fujinomiya-san!
Masamune-sama...
So I was right.
I saw someone who looked like you in
the lobby and thought it might be you.
Are you here to visit someone?
No, I'm here to get some test results.
Oh, my. Are you not feeling well?
Nah. There's nothing wrong at all.
That's actually sorta the problem...
Can we give you a ride?
Huh?
You can tell me all about it at my house.
Here you are.
Oh, um, th-thanks.
You'd better know what'll happen
if you do something to my lady.
I'm not gonna do anything!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Masamune-sama.
These are a gift from Kyoto.
Thanks.
So, is something troubling you?
The fact that I'm discussing
health issues with Fujinomiya Neko
is a bit short-sighted, even for me.
Well... is there such a thing as
stress affecting your body when there's
technically nothing wrong with you?
That's weird, right?
If we're talking about stress...
It should've been way worse when I was
hiding my origins and plotting my revenge...
Is it because I still have
something I haven't said?
But if I say that,
it'll affect Koiwai-san, too.
Or perhaps...
Maybe the cause is the fact that
you don't have a lie to tell anymore.
I don't have a lie to tell?
I have the perfect phrase to describe
you right now, Masamune-sama.
And what's that?
Burnout syndrome.
Seeing your revenge through
was your reason to live.
That was your lifelong wish.
But that must mean that it having
disappeared suddenly is still a shock to you,
despite the fact that you're
going out with Aki-sama now.
Because you don't actually love her.
But... I...
Used to love her back then?
Is the past that important?
Huh?
I know this may not matter now,
but the truth is...
I met you once before, a long time ago.
Long before Aki-sama.
Huh?
Do you not remember?
It was my relative Yuriko-neesan's wedding.
Your family was invited due to
the groom's business relations.
H-Huh?!
Sorry!
Even after all that, I don't remember it!
I can't blame you for not remembering.
I had half forgotten about it myself
while I was wondering if I should
have my surgery or not.
Masamune-sama, do you remember
being here and saying,
"You don't actually like me, either"?
Well, yeah, of course...
I remember that much...
It frustrated me, but I couldn't argue.
Because I was trying to start a game of love
just based on my meager memories.
Fujinomiya-san...
But you see, Masamune-sama...
Even if my original intentions were dishonest,
I'm not going to disparage
the person I've been since.
Because...
I can say this without any hesitation now.
The past doesn't matter.
I've fallen in love with you right now.
What about you?
I recommend casting aside your
pretenses and preconceptions.
So that you stop
blaming yourself, as well.
Of course... I wouldn't mind
helping you with that if I can.
Hold it right there!
Please move, my lady!
I'm going to extinguish this fool at once.
Wha— Shidou-san! Calm down!
There's nothing to worry about, Shidou.
No mistakes will be happening here.
Wait, this is...
I think I'm also in need of casting aside
my pretenses and preconceptions.
Masamune-sama, let me get
you some more coffee.
Messages
Cruel Princess
You went to the hospital, didn't you?
Was everything okay?
Cruel Princess
Pretenses and preconceptions, huh?
If there's a haze over my eyes right now...
If there's some other truth...
Then I sure the hell would
like to know what it is!
Huh?!
You okay?
Come on, now.
What's the matter?
Crap! Was that my fault?
I'm really sorry! Are you okay?
Master?
Grapel
Pig's Foot...